Guide to the Kiwanis Club of Houston records, 1919-2017 MS 619
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IX: Foundation, 182865
  - Foundation Gant Requests, 183733
    - Grant Application: Christian Community Service Center, 2011-2012; 182975 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Grant Application: Child Builders, 2011; 182976 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Grant Application: Center for Hearing and Speech, 2011-2012; 182977 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Grant Application: Yellowstone Academy, 2011-2012; 182978 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Grant Application: Children at Risk, 2011; 182979 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Grant Application: Sam Houston Area Council Boy Scouts, 2011; 182981 (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Grant Application: Periwinkle Foundation, 2010-2011; 182982 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Grant Application: Child Builders, 2011; 182984 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Grant Application: Harris Foundation, 2012-2013; 182985 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Grant Application: Periwinkle Foundation, 2012; 182986 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Grant Application: New School in the Heights, 2012-2012; 182987 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Grant Applications, 2010-2011; 182989 (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Grant Application: Christian Community Service Center, 2010-2011; 182990 (Box 44, Folder 48)
    - Grant Application: Center for Hearing and Speech, 2010; 182992 (Box 44, Folder 49)
    - Grant Application: Yellowstone Academy, 2010; 182993 (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Grant Application: Aldine Youth, Inc., 2010-2011; 182994 (Box 44, Folder 51)
    - Grant Application: Arrow Child and Family Ministries' Freedom Place, 2011-2012; 182995 (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - Grant Application: Nehemiah Center, Inc., 2011-2012; 182999 (Box 44, Folder 53)
    - Grant Application: Weather Research Center, 2011-2012; 183000 (Box 44, Folder 54)
    - Grant Application: Young Life, 2012; 183001 (Box 44, Folder 55)
    - Grant Application: Escape Family Recourse Center, 2012; 183002 (Box 44, Folder 56)
    - Grant Application: Houston Achievement Place, 2011-2012; 183003 (Box 44, Folder 57)
    - Grant Application: Depression + Bipolar Support Alliance, 2012; 183004 (Box 44, Folder 58)
    - Grant Application: Boys + Girls Country, 2012; 183005 (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Foundation Finances, 183734
    - Foundation Minutes and Financial Reports, 1972-1974; 183006 (Box 44, Folder 60)
    - Foundation Minutes and Financial Reports, 1974-1976; 183007 (Box 44, Folder 61)
    - Foundation Minutes and Financial Reports, 1976-1977; 183008 (Box 44, Folder 62)
    - Foundation Minutes and Financial Reports, 1977-1979; 183009 (Box 44, Folder 63)
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1943-1946; 183010 (Box 44, Folder 64)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1966-1967; 183011 (Box 44, Folder 65)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1967-1968; 183012 (Box 44, Folder 66)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1968-1969; 183013 (Box 44, Folder 67)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1969-1970; 183014 (Box 44, Folder 68)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1970-1971; 183015 (Box 44, Folder 69)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1971-1972; 183016 (Box 44, Folder 70)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1976-1977; 183017 (Box 44, Folder 71)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1977-1978; 183018 (Box 44, Folder 72)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1979-1980; 183019 (Box 44, Folder 73)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1981-1982; 183020 (Box 44, Folder 74)
    - Foundation: Audited Financial Statements, 1989; 183021 (Box 44, Folder 75)
    - Foundation: Audit Program, 1981, 1982; 183022 (Box 44, Folder 76)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 183028 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1972-1973; 183029 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1973-1974; 183030 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1974-1975; 183031 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1975-1976; 183032 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1976-1977; 183033 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1977-1978; 183034 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1978-1979; 183035 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1979-1980; 183036 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1980-1981; 183037 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1981-1982; 183038 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1982-1983; 183039 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1985-1988; 183040 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1985-1993; 183041 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Foundation Disbursement Journal, 1978-1981; 183027 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Foundation Ledger Book, 1983; 183023 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Foundation Ledger Sheets, 1983-1985; 183025 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Foundation Salary Sheets, 1973-1979; 183026 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Foundation Investment Ledgers, 1980s; 183042 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Disbursement Journal, 183024 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Ledger Book, 1968-1972; 183045 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Cash Ledger Book, 1972-1989; 183046 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Selection of Beneficiaries- Hirsch Trust, 1987; 183047 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Re: Kiwanis/ Winifred Hirsch Benefit Invitations (list), 1/7/1989; 183048 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Estate of Maurice Hirsch, 1990; 183049 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Estate of Winifred Busby Hirsch, Probate Court, 1990; 183050 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Hirsch Fellow File, 1990; 183051 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Hirsch Estate File, 1991; 183052 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - General and Mrs. Maurice Hirsch Memorial Gift, 183053 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Winifred Busby Hirsch Charitable Trust, 1992; 183054 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Audit of Hirsch Trust, 1992; 183055 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Hirsch Trust Statements, 183056 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Maurice Hirsch Mineral Deed and Correction, 1992-1993; 183057 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1972-1973; 183058 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1982-1983; 183060 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1983-1984; 183061 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1984-1985; 183062 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1985-1986; 183063 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1986-1987; 183065 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1987-1988; 183066 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1988-1989; 183068 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1989-1990; 183070 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1989-1991; 183071 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1990-1991; 183072 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1991-1992; 183073 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1994; 183075 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 1995-1999; 183077 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Foundation Worksheets, 2002; 183078 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Foundation Statement of Activities, 2005-2006; 183079 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Foundation Budgets, 1968-1974; 183080 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1980-1981; 183081 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1981-1982; 183082 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1988-1989; 183083 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1989-1990; 183084 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1990-1991; 183085 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1991-1992; 183086 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 1992-1993; 183087 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Foundation Frost Bank Statements, 1994-1999; 183091 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Foundation Frost Bank Statements, 2000-2003; 183092 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 2002-2003; 183093 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Foundation Bank Statements, 2009; 183094 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Frost Bank Authorized Signers, 183095 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Frost Bank Interest Income and Ad Valorem Statement, 183096 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Frost Bank Safe Deposit Box, 183097 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Cowen and Co. (Broker), 1980-1986; 183098 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1985-1988; 183099 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1988-1989; 183100 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1989-1990; 183101 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1990-1991; 183102 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1991-1992; 183103 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1992-1994; 183104 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1994-1996; 183105 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Foundation Cowen and Co. Account Statements, 1996-1999; 183106 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - US Trust Co. of Texas Statements, 2002-2003; 183107 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - US Trust Co. of Texas Statements, 2003-2004; 183108 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - US Trust Co. of Texas Statements, 2005-2006; 183109 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - US Trust Co. of Texas Statements, 2006-2007; 183110 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Foundation U.S. Trust Account, 2003-2007; 183111 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Hirsch Estate Interest, 183112 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Stock, 183113 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Dividends and Interest Due, 1985-1992; 183114 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Robert E. Lee- Donations to Foundation, 183115 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Robert E. Lee- Donations to Foundation, 183116 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Savings Account, 183117 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Brokers, 183118 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Certificate of Deposit, 183119 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Bonds, 183120 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Mutual Funds, 183121 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Texas Committee Time Deposit, 183122 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Student Loan Fund, 183123 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Merrill Lynch Portfolio, 2007-2008; 183124 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Charles Schwab Account, 183125 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Lehman Brothers, 183126 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Income Policy, 183127 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Texas Workforce Commission Tax Rate Notices, 2006-2008; 183128 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Employees Wage and Tax Statements, 183129 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Employers Quarterly Reports, 1966-1976, 1978; 183130 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Employers Quarterly Reports, 1977-1990s; 183131 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Employer's Annual Federal Unemployment Tax Return #940, 183132 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Tax Exemptions, 183133 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Federal Tax Returns, 183134 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Federal Tax Returns, 1978-1993; 183135 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Tax Exempt Status fillings, 1972-1985; 183136 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Tax Exempt Status Fillings, 1985-1993; 183137 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Tax Return, 1994; 183138 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Tax Return, 1995; 183139 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Income Statement Ride On, 1995; 183140 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Insurance Alliance Policy, 2007-2009; 183141 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Workers Comp and Liability Policy, 183142 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Foundation Legal Files, 183735
    - Foundation Legal (1), 183143 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Foundation Legal (2), 183144 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Mary Teresa Rodriguez Bankruptcy Court Transcript and Articles, 183145 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Foundation Programs and Projects, 183736
    - "Amigos" Parent Prep Guide, 2011; 183146 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - "Amigos Volunteer Training Handbooks, 2010, 2012; 183147 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Periwinkle Foundations- Making a Mark, 183148 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Growing Up in Houston, 2006-2008; 183149 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Kan Festival File, 183150 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Bear Creek School Thank you Notes, 183151 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Endowment Campaign Committee, 183152 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Endowment Campaign Brochure, 1996; 183153 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Fred Heitmann (Donations, etc.), 183154 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Endowment Campaign Correspondence, 1997; 183155 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Endowment Campaign Gift, 183156 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Endowment Campaign Thanks-Yous, 1996-1997; 183157 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Sealy Fall Classic Bike Ride, 10/2010, 183158 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Sweet Heart Celebration, 1989; 183159 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Capital Fund Drive, 1974-1975; 183160 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Capital Campaign, 2011; 183161 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Bowl-a-thon, 183162 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Thank You Letter for Donations, 9/23/1996; 183163 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Foundation Correspondence, 183164 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Foundation Christmas Party, 1996, 183165 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Foundation Education Committee Seminar, 3/6/1996; 183166 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Foundation Newsletter, 183167 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Foundation Heritage Club, 183168 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Series X: Texas-Oklahoma District, 183169
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: By Laws: (1 of 2), 183170 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: By Laws: (2 of 2), 183171 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: By Laws and Draft Revisions, 183172 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: History, 183173 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: Division 3 Council Minutes, 183174 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: Club Reports Point System, 183175 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: Directories (1 of 2), 183176 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District: Directories (2 of 2), 183177 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District File, 183178 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District Club Rankings, 183179 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District Council Meetings, 2001-2002; 183180 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District Division Reports, 2003-2004; 183181 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Aubrey Irby Recitation- New Orleans, LA, 1981; 183182 (Box 51, Folder 34)
- Series XI: Kiwanis International, 183183
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 183184 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Formulation of New Clubs, 183185 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Brochure, 183186 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Notes (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Bulletin for Kiwanis Officers, 183187 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Texas-Oklahoma meetings, 1969-1990 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Texas-Oklahoma District Foundation (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Memorial Booklets, 183188 (Box 52, Item 1)
  - International Foundations Birthday Celebration, 183189 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - International Assorted Bulletins, 183190 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - "Your Visit to the Kiwanis International Building", 183191 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Club Brochures, 183192 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Kiwanis International Brochures (1 of 2), 183193 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Kiwanis International Brochures (2 of 2), 183194 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - The Boy Builder, 183196 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Kiwanis Counselor's Handbook, 183195 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Club Secretary Manual, 183197 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - "The Birth of Kiwanis" 8" Record, 183198 (Box 53, Item 10)
  - Kiwanis International Directories, 1963-1994, 183199 (Box 53, Item 11)
  - "The Men Who Wear The K" The Story of Kiwanis, 183200 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Series XII: Correspondence, 183201
  - Correspondence, 1999; 183202 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Lt. Governor, 183203 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence- Hotels, 183204 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence re: Billboards, 1990; 183205 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Assorted Correspondence, 183206 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Series XIII: Legal Documents, 183207
  - Legal Files, 183208 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Legal- Lease #98 Mary F. Lambert and Refugio Oil and Gas Co., 3/21/1925; 183209 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Houston Club Constitution and Bylaws, 183210 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Series XIV: Ephemera, 183211
  - Newspaper Clippings c., 1920s; 183212 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - News Paper Scrapbook, 1920s; 183215 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - OS news paper scrapbook, 1919, 1929; 183461 (Box 54, Item 1)
  - Proclamation- Mexico-United States Friendship Week, 1974; 183235 (Box 54, Item 2)
  - Proclamation- Kiwanis International Day, 1998; 183236 (Box 54, Item 3)
  - Proclamation- Astro Bluebonnet Bowl Week, 1976; 183237 (Box 54, Item 4)
  - Proclamation- American Freedom Train in Houston Week, 1976; 183238 (Box 54, Item 5)
  - Proclamation- Kiwanis Club of Houston Day, 1994; 183239 (Box 54, Item 6)
  - Proclamation- Kiwanis Kan Festival and Houston Food Bank Day, 1991; 183240 (Box 54, Item 7)
  - Proclamation- Kiwanis Golden Anniversary, 1969; 183241 (Box 54, Item 8)
  - Proclamation- General and Mrs. Maurice Hirsch Remembrance Day, 183242 (Box 54, Item 9)
  - Kiwanis Club of Houston Charter, 1919; 183462 (Box 55, Item 1)
  - Kiwanis Club of Houston Charter, 1962; 183463 (Box 55, Item 2)
  - The Objects of Kiwanis International, 183464 (Box 55, Item 3)
  - Shuttle Launch Poster "Best Wishes!", 1997; 183246 (Box 55, Item 4)
  - NASA Collage Poster Board for SS Challenger, 183247 (Box 55, Item 5)
  - Kiwanis Objectives, 1945; 183465 (Box 55, Item 6)
  - Poster Print of Park- 15 years of Excellence, 1979-1994; 183234 (Box 56, Item 1)
  - Spencer Home for Boys thank you Poster Board, 1/8/1979; 183231 (Box 56, Item 2)
  - Cartoon Board of Visit to Deep Water Plan, 1927; 183245 (Box 56, Item 3)
  - Mounted excerpt from Industries of Houston, 1884-1885- Reichardt, Wm., Groceries. Autographed by Robert Reichardt, 1959 to Downtown Kiwanis Club of Houston, 183243 (Box 56, Item 4)
  - Kiwanis Club of Houston Poster, 183244 (Box 56, Item 5)
  - "My Kiwanis Year" Scrapbook Pages, Robert L. Rowan Jr. President, 1982-1982; 183229 (Box 56, Item 6)
  - Kiwanis International Scrapbook- T.P. Wier, 183213 (Box 56, Item 7)
  - Kiwanis Club of Houston- Guest Book, 1974-1988; 183230 (Box 56, Item 8)
  - "Kiwanis in Action" Curtis O. Johnson, President, 1978-1979; 183214 (Box 56, Item 9)
  - "Thank You from the children of Camp Periwinkle" Painted Tile, 183467 (Box 56, Item 10)
  - Celebrations of Triumph and Courage Camp periwinkle, 183468 (Box 56, Item 11)
  - The Splendid Review, 183469 (Box 56, Item 12)
  - Child art work, water color, in the field, Philip Kocurek, 183470 (Box 56, Item 13)
  - Flags, Patches, and Badges, 183216 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Kiwanis International Seal, 183225 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Print Block, 183219 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - John Kirby Ewing Nametag- Host Chairman International Convention, 1985-1986; 183218 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - "Camp for All" Wood Block Ornament, 183220 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Ornament, 183221 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Durell Carothers Past President Button, 183223 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Kiwanis Club Houston, Texas Charter Print Block, 183224 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Kiwanis International Seals, 183217 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - "50 Golden Years" Gold Medallion in Glass- Kiwanis Club of Orilla Ontario, 1924-1974; 183226 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Metal Wall Plaques: Will C. Miller, 10th President; Dr. William Jacobs, 2nd President, 183227 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Texas Sequicentennial Metal Plaque, 1986; 183809 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Brochure Scrapbook, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Patch Decorated Banner (1 of 3), 183493 (Drawer 183)
  - Patch Decorated Banner (2 of 3), 183494 (Drawer 184)
  - Patch Decorated Banner (3 of 3), 183495 (Drawer 185)
  - Poster of Shuttle Launch: "Happy 67th 'Dowtown Kiwanis' from Metropolitan Houston Kiwanis", 2/5/1986; 183496 (Drawer 186)
- Series XV: Photographs, 183248
  - "Kiwanis in Action" Scrapbook Photos (1 of 2), 1976-1977; 183249 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - "Kiwanis in Action" Scrapbook Photos (2 of 2), 1976-1977; 183250 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - "Kiwanis in Action" President Curtis O. Johnson Scrapbook Photos (1 of 3), 1978-1979; 183251 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - "Kiwanis in Action" President Curtis O. Johnson Scrapbook Photos (2 of 3), 1978-1979; 183252 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - "Kiwanis in Action" President Curtis O. Johnson Scrapbook Photos (3 of 3), 1978-1979; 183253 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - "My Kiwanis Year" Robert L. Rowan Jr. Scrapbook Photos (1 of 4), 1982-1983; 183254 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - "My Kiwanis Year" Robert L. Rowan Jr. Scrapbook Photos (2 of 4), 1982-1983; 183255 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - "My Kiwanis Year" Robert L. Rowan Jr. Scrapbook Photos (3 of 4), 1982-1983; 183256 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - "My Kiwanis Year" Robert L. Rowan Jr. Scrapbook Photos (4 of 4), 1982-1983; 183257 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - "Wright," - 1 color photograph, 1983; 183258 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Meeting with Military Affairs Committee; Dr. Decker; Phil Gramm; 2 unlabeled photographs- 17 photographs, 1983; 183259 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Keys and Milton Buie, 14 photographs, 1984; 183260 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Governor's Banquet- 24 photographs, 1984; 183261 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Christmas- 6 polaroids; 20 unlabeled photographs, 1987; 183262 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Periwinkle Golf- 1 photograph, 1998; 183263 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Kids Triathlon (1 of 5), 1998; 183264 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Kids Triathlon (2 of 5), 1998; 183265 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Kids Triathlon (3 of 5), 1998; 183266 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Kids Triathlon (4 of 5), 1998; 183267 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Kids Triathlon (5 of 5), 1998; 183268 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: Periwinkle Bake-a-thon- 1 photograph, 1997-1998; 183269 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: Meeting- 23 photographs, 1997-1998; 183270 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: Meeting- 22 photographs, 1997-1998; 183271 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: Meeting- 23 photographs, 1997-1998; 183272 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: Golf and Lunch- 22 photographs, 1997-1998; 183273 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: Meeting- 24 photographs, 1997-1998; 183274 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Glenn Johnson's File: 23 unlabeled photographs, 1997-1998; 183275 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - 9 photographs and polaroids, 183276 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - 98-530 #5, #37- 3 photographs, 183277 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Presentation of Check from Kiwanis to TCCC/HS- 1 photograph, 183278 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Richard P. Underwoo- 1 black and white photograph, 183279 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook Photographs- Browning Plantation, 183280 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - 5 photographs, 10/1983; 183281 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - 9 black and white photographs, 1985; 183282 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Unlabeled photographs, 1986; 183283 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - 21 photographs, 1988; 183284 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - 20 photographs, 1988; 183285 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - 23 photographs, 1992; 183286 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - 20 photographs, 1992; 183287 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - 24 photographs, 1992-1993; 183288 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - 11 photographs, 1993; 183289 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - 15 photographs, 2/1993; 183290 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - 9 photographs, 2/1993-3/1993; 183291 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - 11 photographs, 3/1993-4/1993; 183292 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - 25 photographs, 1993; 183293 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - 25 photographs, 1993; 183294 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - 12 photographs, 1993; 183295 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - 25 photographs, 9/1993; 183296 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - 25 photographs, 9/1993-10/1993; 183297 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - 25 photographs, 9/1993-10/1993; 183298 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - 25 photographs, 10/1993-12/1993; 183299 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - 25 photographs, 12/1993; 183300 (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - 19 photographs, 1/994-2/1994; 183301 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - 24 photographs, 2/1994; 183302 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - 24 photographs, 3/1994; 183303 (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - 23 photographs, 4/1994-6/1994; 183304 (Box 58, Folder 56)
  - 25 photographs, 6/1994-7/1994; 183305 (Box 58, Folder 57)
  - 25 photographs, 7/1994-8/1994; 183306 (Box 58, Folder 58)